So hey everybody
I'm Jae
This is Java
And we're the admins of the furry tech room
on Matrix as you may know
So five years ago
Day for day
On this day
Was created the Furry Tech room
And when we originally joined the room
Everything was kind of a desert
Like
Only join and part messages
Only occasional REAL messages
And over the years
Being active in this room
A small community started forming
and
at some point, after some
gory spam attacks
let's say it like this
we gained admin permissions in the room
and this is where we really took over it
to maintain it
Over the years, the road wasn't that simple
You probably remember the big spam attacks of last year
which
funnily enough
pulled the room on the top
on the top of the room list on matrix.org
when we had around 15k members
most of them being spam bots
which prompted us to do multiple room upgrades
to the version we all know and love right now
Even tho this road was a bit bumpy
Today we still have a small community of active people
probably the biggest furry community on Matrix?
...that is SFW of course
So...
Java: "mostly"
yes, mostly
so we wanted to thank everybody for
being part of this community
and...
little gift
to celebrate those five years spent together
we decided to commission a little new
room icon
to avoid stealing art from someone
so...
Happy anniversary I guess
Happy anniversary!
and see you in the room
and let's hope
this continues
for many many years more
At least for five more
At least, five more, let's try to do that
well, seeya everyone!